G. Bromley Oxnam Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Notes, Miscellaneous Papers, Records and Reports, 1895-1960 (Box 101-109)
  - Notes and Papers, 1895-1958 (Box 101)
    - Municipal Administration, 1915-1916
    - Papers on the Literature of Social Protest, 1921 (Box 102)
    - Inter-Church Survey, 1912-1922
    - Boston University, Boston, Mass., Miscellaneous Notes, 1927-1928 (Box 103)
    - Life and Teaching of Jesus, circa 1915 (Box 104)
    - American Seminar Notes, Europe and Washington, 1934-1941
    - University of Southern California, Los Angeles, Calif., Notes, 1919-1921
    - Book Notes, 1895-1943
    - The Syrian Christian, 1919 (Box 105)
    - Sun Yat-sen, undated
    - Thomas Masaryk, undated
    - Lenin, Vladimir Illich, undated
    - Confucius, undated
    - Miscellaneous, 1902-1958
  - Records and Reports, 1895-1960 (Box 106)
    - Miscellaneous Personal Record, 1895-1923
    - Memorandum of Prosecutions under California Criminal Syndicalist Law, 1919-1924 (Box 107)
    - Minutes of Area Meetings, District Superintendents, Omaha, Nebr., Area, 1936-1939
    - Library Accession Records
    - Library Accession Records (Box 108)
    - Library Accession Records (Box 109)
    - Report to Northeastern Jurisdictional Conference Committee on Episcopacy, 1940
    - Avery Reports, Survey of Board of Education of Los Angeles, Calif., 1922
    - Miscellaneous, 1925-1960
- Miscellany, 1823-1963 (Box 110-111)
  Early newspapers, biographical material, church statistics, newspaper clippings, printed matter, notes, memoranda, and photographs.
  Grouped by subject or type of material.
  - Biographical, 1891-1963 (Box 110)
  - Church Statistics, 1949-1960
  - Ralph W. Hufferd Case, 1934-1939
  - Protestantism Today, 1949
  - Open Road, 1949
  - Norman Thomas, 1931
  - John Wesley, 1936-1937
  - New England Methodism, 1923-1890
  - DePauw University, Greencastle, Ind., 1928-1936
  - General
  - Photographs, 1872-1958, (4 folders); (1 vol.) (Box 111)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1944-1946
  - Printed Matter, 1923-1960
- Scrapbooks, 1912-1960 (Box 112-137)
  Mounted memoranda, records, reports, notes, church bulletins, programs, early sermons and lecture outlines, miscellaneous papers, printed matter, and newspaper and magazine clippings.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Barca Class, Los Angeles, Calif., 1912-1913 (Box 112)
  - Miscellaneous California Clippings, 1913-1927
  - Bulletin City Parish, 1924-1927
  - Miscellaneous Clippings (Box 113)
    - 1929
    - 1930-1932 (Box 114)
    - 1930 (Box 115)
    - 1931 (Box 116)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 117)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 118)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 119)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 120)
  - Programs, 1936-1937 (Box 121)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings, May 1936
  - Miscellaneous Clippings and Programs (Box 122)
    - 1937-1938
    - 1939-1940 (Box 123)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 124)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 125)
    - 1945 (Box 126)
    - 1946 (Box 127)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 128)
    - 1949 (Box 129)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 130)
    - 1952 (Box 131)
    - 1953 (Box 132)
  - Hearing clippings, 1953 (Box 133)
  - Miscellaneous clippings (Box 134)
    - 1954
    - 1954 (Box 135)
    - 1955-1957 (Box 136)
    - 1958-1960 (Box 137)